(Sheldon:)He's in my spot.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, make him stop being naked
in my spot.
(Leonard:)Howard, what are you doing?
(Howard:)He wasn't using it...
(Howard:)...and I needed a nice cool piece of leather
to wiggle my naked ass on.
(Sheldon:)Get off there.
(Howard:)Give me back my Iron Man helmet.
Give back my parking space.
(Howard:)You don't need a parking space.
You don't have a car.
(Sheldon:)You don't need an Iron Man helmet.
You're not Iron Man.
(Howard:)Well, we appear
to have reached an impasse...
(Howard:)...and, you know, I have to say,
I thought you'd be more upset...
(Howard:)...that your laptop is sitting on my junk.
(Raj:)I didn't pick up on that.
That's a nice touch.
(Amy:)This is so exciting. I'm feeling all tingly.